Wilton Historical Society Photograph Collection
Wilton History Room, Wilton Historical Society
Wilton Historical Society Photograph Collection
1840s-present
Wilton Historical Society (Wilton, Conn.)
PHO
41 linear feet / 4 drawers, 5 boxes, 10 slide carousels, 74 albums and scrapbooks
Wilton History Room, Wilton Historical Society
The Wilton Historical Society Photograph Collection contains photographs, slides, postcards, paintings, line drawings, and other imagery pertaining to Wilton history. Many of these items are loose; some are framed or matted;a large number are stored as they were originally arranged: in family photograph albums, personal scrapbooks, and slide carousels. The bulk of the collection is from the late nineteenth century through the mid-twentieth century.
Restrictions
Collection open for research.
Acquisition Information
The Wilton Historical Society Photograph Collection was compiled by the Wilton Historical Society.
History
1. Wilton Historical Society Photograph Collection
The Wilton Historical Society, founded in 1938, collected extensive photographic materials pertaining to Wilton families, scenery, buildings, and artistic productions. Additions have been made by Carol Russell, Wilton Historical Society Archivist and Wilton Town Historian. The majority of the material included was created by professional photographers, local residents, and Wilton artists.
2. Wilton History Room
The Wilton History Room is a unique collaboration between the Wilton Historical Society (WHS) and the Wilton Library Association (WLA). Compiled beginning in 1938, the archival collections of the Wilton Historical Society had been stored in the 18th century Fitch House. In 1980, the officers and trustees of the WHS, in conversation with the director and board members of the WLA, determined that a climate controlled space, improved organization, and better public accessibility were necessary; and so in January 1984 they established a home for the collection in the Wilton Library. Organization of the collections was supported by the Cudlipp Memorial Fund and undertaken by Carol Russell. The Wilton Historical Society has retained its ownership, while the Wilton Library maintains the collections, and provides access and assistance to patrons.
The Wilton History Room is one of the most complete, organized, and well-staffed historical research facilities, for a town of our size, in Fairfield County. It is financed by the WLA, The Russell Fund, and The History Room Fund.
The Wilton History Room is one of the most complete, organized, and well-staffed historical research facilities, for a town of our size, in Fairfield County. It is supported by the WHS, the WLA, The Russell Fund, The History Room Fund, local non-profit organizations, individual donors, and community volunteers.
Scope and Content of Collection
The bulk of the collection features portraiture of Wilton families and individuals, images of Wilton houses and buildings, economic activities such as farming and animal husbandry, schools and railroads, local scenery and landmarks, and public and private events and celebrations. Photographic types represented in the collection range from early daguerreotypes, ambrotypes, and tintypes, through cabinet cards, late nineteenth and early twentieth century snapshots, and mid- to late twentieth century Polaroids and 35mm slides. In addition to photography, this collection includes original artwork such as paintings and line drawings, scrapbooks containing greeting cards, trade cards, and newspaper clippings, as well as a significant number of late nineteenth and early twentieth century postcards, many depicting scenes from Wilton, Georgetown, and Cannondale.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged by family name, location, or topic. Items are housed in folders, boxes, and albums.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Agriculture.; Art.; Factories.; Historic buildings.; Houses.; Livestock.; Pets.; Photograph albums.; Photographs.; Photography--Negatives.; Postcards.; Railroads.; Roads.; Schools.; Scrapbooks.; Slides (Photography).; Transportation.
Related Collections
Researchers should also consult the Wilton History Room's book collection, and the list of art displayed in the Wilton Library.
Separated Material
Select additional photographs, postcards, drawings, and paintings are in the Wilton Historical Society Museum.
- 1. Houses
  - Photographs in boxes
    - 11 Belden Hill - Deacon Daniel Gregory house, undated; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Item 14)
    - 169 Belden Hill - House, undated; Photograph is one of a series of Lambert Corner, all in P-OS-4, from the 1989 Architectural Survey. (Box P-OS-4, Item 44)
    - Betts Store and Lambert family tenant house, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 7)
    - 37 Cannon Road - House, undated; Photograph is one of a series of Lambert Corner, all in P-OS-4, from the 1989 Architectural Survey. (Box P-OS-4, Item 55)
    - 226 Cannon Road - House, undated; Photograph is one of a series of Lambert Corner, all in P-OS-4, from the 1989 Architectural Survey. (Box P-OS-4, Item 39a, 39b, 39c, 39d, 39e)
    - Cannon-Miller family - Carriage house, undated; Photograph is one of a series of Lambert Corner, all in P-OS-4, from the 1989 Architectural Survey. (Box P-OS-4, Item 57)
    - 36 Chestnut Hill Road - House, undated; Photograph is one of a series of Lambert Corner, all in P-OS-4, from the 1989 Architectural Survey. (Box P-OS-4, Item 56a, 56b, 56c)
    - 294 Chestnut Hill - House, undated; Photograph is one of a series of Lambert Corner, all in P-OS-4, from the 1989 Architectural Survey. (Box P-OS-4, Item 36)
    - 196 Danbury Road - House, undated; Photograph is one of a series of Lambert Corner, all in P-OS-4, from the 1989 Architectural Survey. (Box P-OS-4, Item 38)
    - 198 Danbury Road - Charles Comstock house, 1989; Photograph is one of a series of Lambert Corner, all in P-OS-4, from the 1989 Architectural Survey. (Box P-OS-4, Item 35)
    - 444 Danbury Road - House, undated; Photograph is one of a series of Lambert Corner, all in P-OS-4, from the 1989 Architectural Survey. (Box P-OS-4, Item 45)
    - 503 Danbury Road - William Nichols house, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 1a, 1b)
    - Danbury Road - William Nichols house, undated; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Item 27, 28)
    - Davenport family - Outhouse, undated; Photograph is one of a series of Lambert Corner, all in P-OS-4, from the 1989 Architectural Survey. (Box P-OS-4, Item 51)
    - Garden family - House and outhouse, undated; Photograph is one of a series of Lambert Corner, all in P-OS-4, from the 1989 Architectural Survey. (Box P-OS-4, Item 52)
    - Harre, John C. - Alexander Resseguie house, 1738; This is an original watercolor kept on display in the Wilton History Room. (Box P-OS-5, Item 6)
    - Harre, John C. - Alexander Sloan house, 1731; This is an original watercolor kept on display in the Wilton History Room. (Box P-OS-5, Item 8)
    - Harre, John C. - Matthew Gregory house, 1740; This is an original watercolor kept on display in the Wilton History Room. (Box P-OS-5, Item 7)
    - Homes and buildings in Cannondale, circa 1987; This is a box of slides; it includes a script. (Box SL-8, Item *)
    - House architecture, undated; This is a box of slides. The houses featured are mostly from Wilton, and some text is included. (Box SL-7, Item *)
    - 190 Hurlbutt Street - Knapp family house, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 9)
    - 190 Hurlbutt Street - Knapp family house, undated; Photograph is one of a series of Lambert Corner, all in P-OS-4, from the 1989 Architectural Survey. (Box P-OS-4, Item 37b)
    - 257 Hurlbutt Street - House, undated; Photograph is one of a series of Lambert Corner, all in P-OS-4, from the 1989 Architectural Survey. (Box P-OS-4, Item 58a, 58b, 58c, 58d, 58e)
    - 257 Hurlbutt Street - Raymond-Ambler family house, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 2)
    - 257 Hurlbutt Street - Raymond-Ambler family house - Well-sweep, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 3)
    - Lambert family - House, undated; Photograph is one of a series of Lambert Corner, all in P-OS-4, from the 1989 Architectural Survey. (Box P-OS-4, Item 53)
    - Miscellaneous houses and archeology in Wilton, undated; This is a box of slides featuring the Lambert and Fitch houses, miscellaneous other Wilton houses, and an archeological dig at Lambert corner. (Box SL-9, Item *)
    - 15 Old Danbury Road - House, undated; Photograph is one of a series of Lambert Corner, all in P-OS-4, from the 1989 Architectural Survey. (Box P-OS-4, Item 43a)
    - Outhouse, undated; Photograph is one of a series of Lambert Corner, all in P-OS-4, from the 1989 Architectural Survey. (Box P-OS-4, Item 60)
    - Schenck family - House, undated; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Item 64)
    - Sharp Hill Road - Bedient family homestead, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 8)
    - Sturges Ridge Road - David Miller house, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 4)
    - Sturges Ridge Road - Levi Coley house, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 6)
    - Wilton's old houses, undated; This is a box of slides. (Box SL-6, Item *)
  - Photographs in file cabinets
    - Architectural Survey of Houses and Buildings in Wilton, 1978; Files contain contact prints and negatives. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 737, 738)
    - Belden Hill - Houses, 1930 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 17)
    - 11 Belden Hill Road - Gregory family house, 1975 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 224)
    - 45 Belden Hill Road - Whyte family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 655)
    - 83 Belden Hill Road - Gregory family house, 1822 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 480)
    - 83 Belden Hill Road - Gregory family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 632)
    - 130 Belden Hill Road - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 639)
    - 160 Belden Hill Road - Gregory family house, 1826 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 481)
    - 169 Belden Hill Road - Gregory family house, 1975 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 257)
    - 169 Belden Hill Road - Gregory family house, undated; Includes undated exterior and interior views. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 228, 230, 273, 656)
    - 169 Belden Hill Road - Gregory family house, circa 1890; Files include postcards and photographs. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 229, 285, 834)
    - 180 Belden Hill Road - Gregory family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 256)
    - 215 Belden Hill Road - Cronin-Goldsmith family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 859)
    - 227 Belden Hill Road - James family house, 1965 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 482)
    - 242 Belden Hill Road - Gregory family house, 1965 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 483)
    - 297 Belden Hill Road - Williams family house, 1965 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 486)
    - 302 Belden Hill Road - Sturges family house, 1963 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 669)
    - 304 Belden Hill Road, Tourtellot family - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 300)
    - 311 Belden Hill Road - Gilbert family house, 1965 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 489)
    - 322 Belden Hill Road - Gregory family house, 1965 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 490)
    - 332 Belden Hill Road - Benedict family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 119)
    - 368 Belden Hill Road - Gregory family house, 1965 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 484)
    - 432 Belden Hill Road - Gregory family house, 1965 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 487)
    - 468 Belden Hill Road - Keeler family house, 1965 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 488)
    - Belden Hill Road - House, 1930 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 856)
    - Belden Hill Road - LaValle family house, 1965 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 485)
    - 89 Borglum Road - Borglum family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 970)
    - Cannon Crossing Mill - Curtis family house, 1922 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 575)
    - 8 Cannon Road - Hurlbutt family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 829)
    - 33 Cannon Road - Brown family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 624)
    - 131 Cannon Road - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 807)
    - 226 Cannon Road - Patchen family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 455)
    - Cannon Station - Coley-Seeley family house, 1961 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 247)
    - Cannondale - Rounds family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 118)
    - Card family and house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 939)
    - 145 Catalpa Road - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 643)
    - 139 Cedar Road - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 735)
    - Cheese Spring Road - Comstock family house, 1899; Shows house site only. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 721)
    - 80 Chestnut Hill Road - Ferries family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 671)
    - 92 Chestnut Hill Road - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 884)
    - 120 Chestnut Hill Road - Hottelet family house, circa 1930 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 222)
    - 187 Chestnut Hill Road - Webber family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 670)
    - 250 Chestnut Hill Road - Offinger family house and gardens, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 940)
    - 306 Chestnut Hill Road - Abbott family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 747)
    - Chestnut Hill Road - Nash family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 420)
    - Chicken Street - Log family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 231)
    - 3 Church Street - Foster family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 292)
    - 3 Church Street - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 879)
    - Church Street in Georgetown - David Miller family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 511)
    - 22 Danbury Road - Lum family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 908)
    - 26 Danbury Road - Cooper family house, 1965 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 463)
    - 27 Danbury Road - Dunning family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 466)
    - 31 Danbury Road - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 467)
    - 45 Danbury Road - Benedict family house, 1965 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 468)
    - 72 Danbury Road - House, 1965 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 470)
    - 84 Danbury Road - Randle family house, 1975 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 258)
    - 90 Danbury Road - Hastings family house, circa 1890 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 471)
    - 150 Danbury Road, 1772 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 507)
    - 150 Danbury Road, 1784 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 508)
    - 150 Danbury Road, 1928 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 512)
    - 150 Danbury Road, 1973 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 516)
    - 150 Danbury Road, 1937; Includes a postcard. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 526)
    - 150 Danbury Road, circa 1890 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 527)
    - 150 Danbury Road - Batchelder family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 733)
    - 150 Danbury Road - Betts Store and Lambert family house, 1950 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 518)
    - 150 Danbury Road - Lambert family house, undated; Files include photographs, postcards, and negative prints. Interior and exterior views are included. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 509, 510, 513, 514, 515, 520, 521, 522, 523, 524, 525, 528, 530)
    - 150 Danbury Road - Lambert family house, on Town Seal, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 529)
    - 150 Danbury Road - Wilton Historical Society Museum, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 753)
    - 153 Danbury Road - Whittlesey family house, 1965 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 472)
    - 221 Danbury Road - Betts family house and furniture store, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 219)
    - 224 Danbury Road - Betts family house, 1975 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 451)
    - 224 Danbury Road - Betts family house, undated; Undated views. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 449, 450, 452, 453, 454)
    - 224 Danbury Road - Betts family house, 1965 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 457, 460)
    - 232 Danbury Road - Gregory family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 271)
    - 249 Danbury Road - Fitch family house, 1925; Site operated by the Wilton Historical Society. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 443)
    - 249 Danbury Road - Fitch family house, 1979; Site operated by the Wilton Historical Society. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 476)
    - 249 Danbury Road - Fitch family house, undated; These images are undated. Site operated by the Wilton Historical Society. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 441 444, 445, 722, 726)
    - 249 Danbury Road - Fitch family house, 1890; File 475 includes interior and furnishings. Site operated by the Wilton Historical Society. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 442, 475)
    - 249 Danbury Road - Fitch family house, 1965; File 474 includes an aerial view. File 473 includes a view of the kitchen. Site operated by the Wilton Historical Society. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 464, 465, 469, 473, 474)
    - 249 Danbury Road - Van Wych family house, 1965; This file includes a postcard. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 458)
    - 253 Danbury Road - White family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 233)
    - 255 Danbury Road - Ogden family house - Interior, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 366, 366)
    - 300 Danbury Road in Crossways - Comstock family house, 1977 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 416)
    - 354 Danbury Road - Robinson family house, 1920 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 561)
    - 405 Danbury Road - Marvin family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 236)
    - 405 Danbury Road - Marvin family house and tavern restoration, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 739)
    - 415 Danbury Road - Betts family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 174)
    - 420 Danbury Road - Sackman family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 876)
    - 426 Danbury Road - Hansen family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 695)
    - 426 Danbury Road - Miller family house, 1961 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 577)
    - 436 Danbury Road - Cannon-Miller family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 627)
    - 436 Danbury Road - Miller family house and carriage barn, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 578)
    - 444 Danbury Road - Marvin family house, circa 1900 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 622)
    - 462 Danbury Road - Hurlbutt family house, 1934 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 831)
    - 475 Danbury Road - Hurlbutt family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 828)
    - 487 Danbury Road - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 901)
    - 493 Danbury Road - Nichols family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 579)
    - 516 Danbury Road - Cole family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 614)
    - 530 Danbury Road - Betts family house, 1974 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 268)
    - 539 Danbury Road - Belden family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 1)
    - 555 Danbury Road - Wood family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 744)
    - 967 Danbury Road - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 944)
    - 969 Danbury Road - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 900)
    - Danbury Road - Angelique Betts house, 1929 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 269)
    - Danbury Road - Batchelder family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 205)
    - Danbury Road - Bethel-Nichols family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 274)
    - Danbury Road - Church family house, 1970 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 207)
    - Danbury Road - Gagg family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 890)
    - Danbury Road - Gaylord family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 195)
    - Danbury Road - Hyatt family house, 1965 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 227)
    - Danbury Road - Whitlock family house, 1760 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 193)
    - Danbury Road - Whittlesey-Betts family house, 1921 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 208)
    - Danbury Road, Georgetown - Ranholm family house, 1910 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 849)
    - Danbury Road, Norwalk - House, 1965 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 461)
    - 2 DeForest Road - Mead family house, 1894 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 254)
    - 5 DeForest Road - Marbles family house, 1935 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 220)
    - 156 DeForest Road - DeForest family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 672)
    - 3 Drum Hill Road - Middlebrook family house, 1906 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 76)
    - 34 Drum Hill Road - Richards family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 854)
    - 165 Drum Hill Road - Stewart family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 748)
    - 188 Drum Hill Road - Gedney family house, 1931 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 947)
    - 212 Drum Hill Road - Chapin-Goodwin family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 427)
    - Dumplin Hill - Van Hoosear family house, 1977 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 419)
    - 2 East Meadow Road - Durrie family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 702)
    - Georgetown - Benedict family house, 1975 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 96)
    - Georgetown - Seeley family house, 1912 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 250)
    - 3 Godfrey Place - Bowditch family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 658)
    - 6 Godfrey Place - Goslee family house, 1980 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 729)
    - 39 Grumman Hill Road - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 897)
    - 83 Grumman Hill Road - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 730)
    - Grumman Hill - Post family house, 1975 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 199)
    - Grumman Road - Grumman family house, 1881 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 235)
    - 10 Honey Hill - Bikel family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 712)
    - Huckleberry Hills - Moriarity family house, 1975 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 225)
    - Huckleberry Woods - Mills family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 232)
    - 71 Hurlbutt Street - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 968)
    - 77 Hurlbutt Street - Stewart family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 368)
    - 90 Hurlbutt Street - Rosenbaum family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 673)
    - 123 Hurlbutt Street - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 769)
    - 126 Hurlbutt Street - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 768)
    - 132 Hurlbutt Street - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 767)
    - 138 Hurlbutt Street - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 766)
    - 142 Hurlbutt Street - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 765)
    - 142 Hurlbutt Street - Shipman family house, 1960s (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 339)
    - 150 Hurlbutt Street - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 764)
    - 152 Hurlbutt Street - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 763)
    - 152 Hurlbutt Street - Van Hoosear family house, undated; This file includes glass plate negatives. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 960)
    - 155 Hurlbutt Street - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 770)
    - 157 Hurlbutt Street - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 761)
    - 158 Hurlbutt Street - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 762)
    - 162 Hurlbutt Street - House, 1995 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 967)
    - 175 Hurlbutt Street - Van Hoosear family house, 1975 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 260)
    - 187 Hurlbutt Street - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 760)
    - 190 Hurlbutt Street - Ketcham-Knapp family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 261)
    - 199 Hurlbutt Street - Wilcek family house and barn, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 937)
    - 245 Hurlbutt Street - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 759)
    - 257 Hurlbutt Street - Ambler-Raymond family house, 1894 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 253)
    - 257 Hurlbutt Street - Ambler-Raymond family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 757)
    - 275 Hurlbutt Street - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 758)
    - 277 Hurlbutt Street - Ambler-Raymond family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 156)
    - 379 Hurlbutt Street - Betsey family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 54)